saycpa.com 2017-06-04

# Privacy Policy - songo CPA

#### __[Last Revised: 29 th December 2015]__

Songo Media Ltd. (“ **We** ”, “ **Us** ” or the “ **Company** “) is the owner of the SONGO CPA Affiliate Program (the “ **Program** “). We respect your privacy and are committed to protect the personal information you (“ **you** ”, “ **your** ” or the “ **Publisher** ” or “ **Advertiser** ” as applicable) share with us in connection with the use of our website at the address www.songo.com (“ **Site** “) and the registration process as specified below. This Privacy Policy is intended to describe our practices regarding the information we may collect from you when you use our Site or register to our Program.

Capitalized terms which are not defined herein, shall have the meaning ascribed to them in our _Terms of Use_  (the “ **Terms** “) which this Privacy Policy (the “ **Privacy Policy** “) is incorporated thereto by reference.

BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, INCLUDING TO THE COLLECTION AND PROCESSING OF THE PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS DEFINED BELOW). IF YOU DISAGREE TO ANY TERM PROVIDED HEREIN, YOU MAY NOT USE THE SITE, SERVICE OR PROGRAM.

###  **Which information we may collect?**

We may collect two types of data and information: The first type of information is non-identifiable and anonymous information (“ **Non-PII** ”). We are not aware of you identity as this type of information includes technical information, automated, anonymous and behavioral information. The second type of information is personal identifiable information (“ **PII** ”). This information may identify an individual or may be of a private or sensitive nature. The PII collected by us is provided by you voluntary and only when you register to the Program and create a Publisher/Advertiser Account (as defined below) or use the _Contact Us_ page. The only PII that we collect is the information you provide in order to open up an account after You register to our Program and become one of our Publishers or Advertisers. This information includes Your: email address, full name, contact number, website address, company name, country , state, physical address, zip code and VAT tax number and You financial information (e.g., banking information, PayPal account, etc.). Note that you can change such personal data through the profile section of your Account as detailed below. **To clarify, when browsing the Site we DO NOT collect PII.**  
We do not collect any PII from you without your approval, which is obtained, inter alia, through your active acceptance to the **_Terms Of Use_** and Privacy Policy.  
The Non-PII is used for statistical purposes and enables us to further develop, customize and improve our Site and Program based on users common preferences and uses.

###  **Publisher and Advertiser Account, how can you register?**

If you are a Publisher or Advertiser legally using our Program You will be provided with an online account (the “ **Account** ”); as part of your registration process you will be asked to fill in identifying information and to choose a username and password with which you shall be able to access your Account. The Account belongs to you and as such, you agree: (a) to keep your password secure and confidential; (b) not to permit others to use the Account; and (c) not to transfer or assign the Account’s password, even temporarily, to a third party. You are solely responsible for anything that happens in the Account and you acknowledge and agree that we cannot and will not be liable to You or any third party for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with these Terms or from any unauthorized use of the Account or any other breach of security pertaining to the Account. You agree to notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of the Account or any other breach of security. You acknowledge and agree that we may provide information about you (including the information available in the Account), to the extent that we are required to do so in connection with or in relation to any legal process or in accordance with any applicable laws. Further, you hereby represent and warrant that the information you fill in during the registration process is accurate and truthful.

###  **Sharing Information with Third Parties** :

The Company will not share any PII it collects with any third party. Notwithstanding, We may disclose PII in the following cases: (a) to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process, subpoena or governmental request; (b) to enforce this Privacy Policy or the Terms, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (c) to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (d) to respond to User’s support requests; (e) respond to claims the rights of third-parties were violated; (f) to respond to claims that contact information (e.g. name, email address, etc.) of a third-party has been posted or transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment; (g) to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of the Company, its users, or the general public; (h) when the Company is undergoing any change in control, including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of its assets; or (i) to collect, hold or manage your PII through the Company’s authorized third party service providers (for example, cloud services), as reasonable for business purposes, which may be located in a country that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction; (j) pursuant to your explicit approval prior to the disclosure; or (k) cooperate with third parties for the purpose of enhancing the user’s experience. For avoidance of doubt, the Company may transfer and disclose Non-PII to third parties at its own discretion.

###  **Deletion or modification of PII or the Account:**

In the event you wish for us to delete your Publisher Account or any PII stored with us, please send us an email to: [**contact@songocpa.com**](mailto:Contact@songocpa.com) and we will make reasonable efforts to delete any such PII pursuant to any applicable privacy laws.

###  **Minors:**

To use the Site and Program, you must be over the age of thirteen (13). We do not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of thirteen (13) and do not wish to do so. We reserve the right to request proof of age at any stage so that we can verify that minors under the age of thirteen (13) are not using the Site or Program.

###  **Security:**

We take a great care in implementing and maintaining the security of the Site and Program, including with regards to the Publisher Account and the information therein. The Company employs industry standard procedures and policies to ensure the safety of its users, and prevent unauthorized use of any such information. However, We do not guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur.

###  **Cookies:**

When you access or use the Site, the Company may use industry-wide technologies such as “cookies” (or similar technologies), which store certain information on your computer and which will allow Us to enable automatic activation of certain features (such as: remember your password when you log in for the next time), and make your service experience much more convenient and effortless. The cookies used by the Site are created per session, does not include any information about you, other than your session key and are removed as your session ends and password information. It is easy to prohibit the Local Storage. Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer’s hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, if you block or erase cookies your online experience may be limited. For the purpose of this section, “ **Cookies** ” shall mean a small text files, given ID tags that are stored on a users’ computer’s browser directory or program data subfolders. Cookies are created when a user uses its browser to visit a website that uses cookies to keep track of the user’s movement within the website, remember a user’s registered login, preferences, and other customization functions.

###  **Direct Marketing:**

You hereby agree that we may use your contact details for the purpose of informing you regarding our products and services which may interest you, and to send to you other marketing material, transmitted to the email address you have provided. You may withdraw your consent via sending a written notice to the Company by email to the following address: **[Please provide your customer service/contact us email address]**

###  **Changes to the Privacy Policy:**

The Terms and this Privacy Policy will govern the use of the Site and any information collected within the Site or Program. The Company reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, so please re-visit this page frequently. We will provide notice of substantial and material changes of this Privacy Policy on the homepage of the Site or we will send you an email regarding such changes to the email address that you may have provided us with. Such substantial changes will take effect seven (7) days after such notice was provided on our Site or sent by email. Otherwise, all other changes to this Privacy Policy are effective as of the stated “Last Revised” date and your continued use of the Site after the Last Revised date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.

###  ** _Have any Questions_** **?**

If you have any questions (or comments) concerning this Privacy Policy, you are welcome to send Us an email at: [**contact@songocpa.com**](mailto:contact@songocpa.com) or use the _Contact Us_ page and we will make an effort to reply within a reasonable timeframe.
